{
    "id": "6324df3a3bf6450f993c34e53e649c41",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns And Adjectives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Have you lost ………………………… marbles?",
            "description": "Your, his, her, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my bag. Which one is …………………………………?",
            "description": "The words yours, his, hers, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My composition is better than ………………………………",
            "description": "The words yours, his, hers, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is taller than ………………………………..",
            "description": "Object pronouns are more common after than.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited all of ……………………………. to my party.",
            "description": "Object pronouns are used after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never had the opportunity to meet any one of ……………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are used after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We went to ……………………………. native place last week.",
            "description": "Your, his, her, our and their are possessive adjectives. They are used before nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "our",
                "ours"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is at the door? It must be .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Whose book is this? It must be ……………………………",
            "description": "The words yours, his, hers, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My dog is white. …………………………. is black.",
            "description": "The words yours, his, hers, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "Their",
                "Theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No one loves you more than ……………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after than.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a friend of ...........................",
            "description": "The words yours, his, hers, ours and theirs are possessive pronouns. They are used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}